[Music]
blessings everyone this is chris kendall
from the rawadvantage.com registered
holistic nutritionist raw food lifestyle
coach and raw chef
today i'm bringing you a what i eat in a
day video based on my last
day in the life video linked below
including three recipes
with curry sushi let's get into it maybe
i like it raw
raw advantage likes it wrong oh baby i
like it raw
yeah baby i like it wrong
all right guys so this is going to be my
first meal in the what i eat in a day
video that is kind of following up the
day in the life from last week so if you
want to see the activity that prompted
this
big smoothie well you're going to want
to check out that other video but
here we're going into exactly what i'm
eating you know the calories some of the
nutrition
stuff and the recipes themselves so
you're going to get three recipes today
i'm pretty sure because it's an
active day or it was an active day it's
going to be an active day
right so i do want to share quickly just
a disclaimer you know i've been doing
this for
over 16 years now as a raw vegan and my
meal size has gone
up over the years when i first started
i'd really be eating like three
four five meals a day i remember eight
bananas for like a big smoothie
yeah that seems like a teeny little
snack now so you know eat for enjoyment
eat as much as you really do enjoy right
in between as much as you enjoy as much
as you can
rather than trying to emulate what i'm
doing and stuff down gigantic quantities
you know it does take some time for the
body to adapt and if you're focusing on
enjoyment and just making sure that
you're satiated and you're eating as
many meals throughout the day
as you require to feel really good and
not feel hungry all the time and
dropping your body weight lower lower
that's the key for success so what is
this lunch smoothie going to be
it's just a very simple banana green
smoothie it's just
a screen smoothie one of my common ones
i don't
usually use kale but uh yeah
i got some kale at the auction for like
a dollar for this organic kale so
we're gonna be using that kale and we
have 19 bananas here
some are smaller some are ones that were
in the fridge so they're kind of
cold and nice we got dd over here
my special kitty here maybe we'll see
dottie as well
but we're just gonna start peeling and
put them in the blender that's
that's really it you know it's nothing
too fancy here so
next recipe is going to be a heck of a
lot more exciting and the next one too
actually the next two recipes i'm making
today
i've never made before in my life
literally you know that's kind of fun
you know i'm again you know 17 years
vegan and over 16 years raw vegan
and i can still make recipes that i've
never had in my life there's such an
abundance such variety
as a chef i like making a lot of
different dishes and
yeah you know i wanted to share
something a little different with you
today so
i'm excited for it it's very rare that
it's not at least pretty good and you
know the worst case scenario
you go hmm didn't really love that one
i'm
probably not gonna make it again you
know it's uh
it's pretty fun it's pretty damn fun
here breaking these bananas up
throw them in the blender and we'll fast
forward this a bit
a little tip with green smoothies what i
like to do is actually put the greens in
the bottom portion not the very bottom
but near the bottom
that way they blend up first so you can
just get them nice and smooth without
needing to blend the smoothie quite as
long so
i'm going to put it down here and then
put the rest of the bananas on top
damn this kale is crispy check that out
it's like
oh listen to that oh yeah
really any greens will do you know i i
use
from spinach to arugula which is one of
my favorites to barley grass juice
powder to iceberg lettuce to romaine
lettuce to celery to boston to
bib to red to cause to green you know
butter lettuce almost any of it is good
you know just
get some greens in rotate them use
different ones you know dandelions you
know
wild edibles you know lots of different
stuff so this is just going to be
the kale smoothie you might be saying
chris you're never going to fit those
bananas in there
we'll see well i think we need to start
blending to get this down
the trusty vitamix you can uh you know
learn more below click my link and you
know
help me out with my banana habit you
know i'm an affiliate so i have this
filthy banana habit
help me out please
the obligatory awkward moment with the
tamper
i don't know to oh we still got lots of
room
so let's get the rest of these suckers
in there
oh it looks like it'll fit hey looks
like it looks pretty perfect yeah
just a bunch six pack you know i like to
bring my six-pack with me wherever i go
bring a six-pack to the
you know to the beach to the bar you
know to a skate park
perfect right edie
three in one peel you see that that was
impressive it always makes me think of
the old disney three and one blow
you know what i'm saying anyone comment
below if you know what i'm talking about
say i typically go through a case of
bananas in a week it's like 100 bananas
and
you know if i'm not eating bananas then
i'm eating other sweet fruit
it's just what's available but bananas
are cheap available year-round super
nutritious they digest
really damn well for me people that talk
about them being mucus forming they're
eating them on ripe
then it does you know but if you're
eating them nice and ripe then they're
really smooth digesting and super good
and nutritious for you
do not buy the fear around hybrid or
you know stuff like that i'll do a whole
video on that if that's interesting to
you guys let me know but
bananas now i'm gonna enjoy them
let's blend this up
[Music]
there we have it that's just meal one of
three today
and i'll give you the nutritional calcs
you know from chronometer i recommend
using that
just to understand what's going on i
don't use it all the time but then you
can start to get the hang of how many
calories you're getting in per day you
know like
what kind of nutrients your
macronutrient ratio so how much protein
carbohydrates and fat you're getting in
your day
and you know it doesn't need to be
micromanaged but over the day week month
even years beneficial to know
what you're doing and that way you can
get really great feedback but
i'm just gonna chow this down you know i
like to drink it fairly slowly but i can
very comfortably eat this in about like
15 minutes
you know gandhi said chew your drink and
drink your food
really great advice no matter what
you're eating if you simply do that
chew your drink and drink your food
meaning chew it until it's drink
you're gonna do a heck of a lot better
you know so i'm gonna take my time
dedicate myself to the smoothie and uh
the moment and we'll see you on the next
recipe
all right so here we are in chronometer
and i'm gonna show you just kind of a
basic
overview of each meal and at the very
end of the video i'm gonna show
a breakdown of all the meals together
and go into the details of exactly what
i got
i have in here kind of fine-tuned for
myself for
an average of about 2775 calories per
day
you can see this meal 13 medium bananas
six small bananas and 200 grams of kale
gave me 1975 calories
uh you know again i normally burn 2775
and so it looks like i'm still requiring
an 800 calorie balance but in reality
this is a pretty active day so i'll be
needing more than that
so if you look here you can see that
i've met 71
of my energy needs for an average day i
got 29.2 grams of protein or amino acids
433 grams of carbohydrate
and 10 grams of fat
72 of my nutritional targets just with
this one meal for the day so over 168
percent of my fiber
over a hundred and ten percent of my
iron 62 percent of my calcium
over 366 percent of my vitamin a doing
good there
over 400 of my vitamin c tons of folate
lots of potassium and again i'm gonna go
into each meal as we go and then the
full breakdown at the end
all right well it's been a jam-packed
day a fun and adventure you're gonna
have to watch the video before to figure
out what happened between uh
lunch and my pre-dinner smoothie and you
know actually before i get into that
recipe i'm going to do a little bit of
pre-prep for the dinner recipe and i'll
let you in a little secret
i'm doing a bit of a fusion i'm doing a
curry
sushi recipe that i've never done before
really excited for it
i'm just playing around in here so
something maybe a little bit sloppy but
we'll we'll see i think it'll spark some
ideas and hopefully you guys will enjoy
it so
for the pre-prep all i'm going to do is
take
300 grams of mushrooms criminy my
personal favorite i absolutely love
these guys
and 300 grams of grape tomatoes and cut
them into little cubes
and then dehydrate them for at least an
hour i probably like an hour and a half
two hours but i don't
quite have that time so i'm just going
to do that so
let's just chop them up and get them in
there
see i want them almost in like a salsa
dice pretty small i'll get them ready
for the front so they dehydrate quicker
i think you get the picture all right so
we got all the beautiful mushrooms it's
quite a bit maybe i overdid it but i do
love mushrooms and i cut them pretty
small i
cut each mushroom into like nine and
sometimes even twelve little cubes
so those would dehydrate a lot faster
now i've got these grape tomatoes or
cherry tomatoes you could use any
tomatoes just trying to get them into a
small little dice
i'm using a little serrated knife
because sometimes tomatoes just squish
it if you don't have a super sharp knife
and
while this is pretty sharp it's not like
crazy sharp so
i'm going to cut these guys in half and
then i'm going to actually cut them
three like that so there we go so i got
three bits and the idea is i want to get
as much of the wet
tomato in size exposed so that when i
dehydrate
they get kind of more crisp and less
watery i want them to be
have a teeny bit of water when you bite
into them but not like wet doesn't make
the sauce
really liquidy so here we go let's go to
the dehydrator room
and now into the excalibur food
dehydrator the best dehydrators in the
business you can use my link to support
my banana habit if you like you know
free shipping
seriously they're the best i recommend
the nine tray just the basic one like
this
so we got the mushrooms just above
center
and the tomatoes right in the center and
i'm going to turn that
right up to about 118 boom
sorry it's a little messy oh gosh how
embarrassing
all right so now that we got that stuff
in the dehydrator and prepped for dinner
i'm starting with my pre-dinner smoothie
yeah this might be like an
hour before but after the skate that's
the other video after the other stuff
i want to recharge up with some fruit so
what do i have here
oh i love mandarin oranges so i have 15
mandarin oranges and i have here the
flex zion vacuum blender
i have both the vitamix and the flex ion
i actually have a video comparison of
the two
in the link below you can learn more
about why i do love a
vacuum blender as well you know but i
also still use the vitamix i love them
both but
for this recipe i'm going to use the
flex ion nice
super smooth texture deeper flavor less
air bubbles in it so it's just
a more enjoyable drink so i'm just going
to peel all these mandarins and
fill that up so let's just give it a go
you ever do this when you're little we
used to do this all the time
let's see carefully peel
no not bad not bad
hello look at me i'm an elephant it's
not a weiner face it's an elephant
yeah there you go and they barely fit in
there in fact that's a little more than
you're supposed to put but i know
this will shrink down to probably down
there so we're gonna put this in put the
lid on oh yeah you can
hear the air getting pumped out put her
on to the base and then close it up
switch to the vacuum setting and we'll
just vacuum it up
[Music]
this is just sucking all the air out
there or as much as it possibly can
which helps with less oxidization when
you're actually making a smoothie which
blends to having higher antioxidant
profile with the finished result
and less air bubbles pretty darn neat
you can actually really taste the
difference and again there's that whole
video
so now we'll just switch to the b blend
go back in just a teeny more and then go
[Music]
yeah come on come on
gotta do it come
there we on sometimes you gotta get
violent
oh there we go finally it's all done so
it's one of my favorite parts just open
this up twist it off
and when you pull this little release
valve you'll see the air go back in so
watch closely
oh do you see that so this made more
than i planned on i'm just going to make
a little bit harder to do the secret new
smoothie that i've never made before so
what i'm gonna do is drink a little bit
down so i'm just gonna have a little bit
of this mandarin
oh yes
hmm i love madrid orange season
we call them christmas oranges here
all right so to make something a little
different you know i've never tried this
before as i said i'm kind of excited to
give it a go
i'm just going to take this mandarin
orange juice or smoothie
and mix it with this guava mango
kombucha i got cases of kombucha for a
crazy deal it's organic high quality
kombucha 70 cents a bottle so
i don't really go crazy on kombucha
generally sometimes i go a year having a
couple you know but
i've had years without any of course but
when i saw him at that price
and good quality and really tasty i
figured i'd give her a go so
make it kind of like a sparkling
smoothie so let's see see if i can pour
this whole bottle in there
oh come on you can do it
there we go perfect that's what i was
looking for now
i'm not going to blend that up instead
i'm just going to
give it a little mix
oh look it's even got a head on
oh wow that's really neat so let's give
this a go
wow that's a pretty tasty one so i'm
gonna
suck this back chill out with my folks
for a little bit and then we'll get into
the dinner prep for the
curry sushi
yeah all right so here we have that
fancy sparkling mandarin orange smoothie
now this isn't the exact kombucha i had
was the closest one i could
see that had similar calories and
similar amount there so
you can see that it's about 790 calories
that we're looking at about 10.7 grams
of protein
175 grams of carbs and 4.1 grams of fat
we're looking at 30 of all my targets
just in this pre-dinner meal
so i mean had some fiber even though you
wouldn't think so it still has
some soluble fiber there and decent
amount of iron 25 percent
almost 49 of your calcium you get a lot
of calcium from oranges it's pretty dang
amazing and navels are way higher
lots of vitamin a that's definitely not
a worry tons of vitamin c not a worry
over half of my folate and potassium and
let's get into the dinner meal that's
going to hit it hard
all right guys so now we're diving into
the grand finale or the dinner recipe
the uh promised curry sushi recipe so
oh i'm pretty excited with this i'm
getting pretty damn hungry that smoothie
went down really nice and
uh i think we're gonna start off by
making the sushi rice now
of course other stuff in the dehydrator
still i've actually given it an hour and
a half so it's looking good i just
checked on it a little bit ago
but what i'm going to start with is the
cauliflower
rice and i'm going to use a technique
that alyssa from raw food romance
actually
created and came up with i've never seen
it before so we have
600 grams of raw cauliflower
so it's going to take this cauliflower
put it directly into the vitamix blender
if you don't have a vitamix blender then
maybe what you're going to want to use
instead
would be a food processor and just
break it up put it in there put it on a
low to medium speed and
just food process it until it makes kind
of like a pilled up rice like texture
but this is a little bit quicker and
easier
and less clean up than using the food
processor
and if you don't know me by now you
don't know that i'm lazy
yeah it might make some fancy stuff but
i'm always going for the quickest
easiest route possible
so that's why i'm using this technique
here and i want to give extra props so
to
list a rocco's romance and her husband
nate both
awesome awesome peeps i got amazing
recipes themselves meal plans and their
new nice cream
book and lots of really cool stuff so
i'll put a link down below to check some
of their stuff out as well you
definitely want to
and this is pretty perfect
just breaking it up in there
there we go on top of mine i can just
break cauliflower and this little stem
end
it's going to chop chop
chop chop chop chop there we go
good thing i cut up my fingers and
the technique that she uses that will
make this into beautiful rice
she calls it the wet chop technique
pretty cool right so what we're going to
do is
fill this up with water so it's all in
water i have
reverse osmosis tap right here so
not getting any weird stuff on it i
definitely recommend getting filtered
water maybe using a brita if you don't
have a whole house system
i'm just going to fill that up so it's
completely covered in water
so you can see that now right and we're
going to put it on the trusty vitamix
blender case
and just turn it on at a really low
speed so we're going to start at the
lowest speed
there we go and just pulse it a little
bit so that we get all of those chunks
in there and we're not pulverizing it
right
there we go
that looks good
that's it make sure there's no big
chunks floating at the top no
it's all ricey in there and then what
we're gonna do
is use a trusty nut milk bag now
all the link below for one of my
favorite nut milk bags this guy is
really really good really helpful we'll
be using this a little bit later in the
recipe too
for laziness and convenience so we're
just going to take this
and dump the water out hopefully you can
see this i can zoom in yeah
that's that's that's the ticket that's
me being lazy again so
pour this in there nope
get this little bit in the corner out
and you really want to squeeze the
liquid out you don't want it to be
watery rice otherwise it's just going to
soak your nori
right so it's going
and squeeze squeeze and twist and
squeeze use those
rubbing muscles
thank you listen for this awesome
awesome technique
i really don't like cleaning the
cleaning the food processor i know
that's
pretty pretty lazy maybe you don't even
have a food processor you invested in
vitamix which i would recommend
if i was going to do any one kitchen
tool obviously besides like a knife
it'd be a vitamix blender again you can
see my links below and support my banana
habit okay so now
in this bag we have some beautiful
cauliflower rice it's gonna
pop it all in here looks beautiful you
could use this in so many ways i mean if
you don't have the nor you could just
make the same curry over top of the rice
you know but
we're making sushi we're going for it so
there we go that's in there
we'll be using this again so i'll set
this aside and i'll just show you look
how beautiful that looks right like
just perfect rice you know it's really
darn nice
rice is nice when it's cauliflower rice
there we go so we have the cauliflower
rice we're just gonna set that aside
and next we're going to get into making
the curry sauce since we have
the bulk of the korean ingredients
dehydrating in the basement in the
excalibur diet so i have here
about 300 grams of carrots
and i'm just going to chop those up
we're going to put those into the
vitamix blender hopefully they go in
there no
they're over oh my god oh geez
just call me the clumsy chef how
embarrassing
put those in there and this time
we're going to blend it on high and use
this tamper now this is me being lazy
again not using a juicer because
i don't like cleaning juicers you know
and
yeah geez someone else wants to juice
for me come on come on
no that this works really darn good so
otherwise you could use
a juicer and if you don't have this then
you could
you know just use some water and it
doesn't taste quite as good this is
this is kind of taking that tip from
cocoa butter veggies 3.0
you can see the link below for that's
gonna be tons of links below but
it's a really good way to flavor that
broth or the sauce
so it's gonna blend this
[Music]
there we go and we're gonna do the same
thing
we're going to dump these carrot bits
into the nut milk bag
rather the carrot puree
there's a teeny bit left no biggie i
usually have to scoop in there with my
hand and
get the stuff stuck to the side
well there we go you can see we have a
little bit left in there i'm not worried
about that
and then we're just going to squeeze
this
into a bowl or you could squeeze it back
in the blender but i didn't want any
drips on the countertop
so squeezing this into the bowl
and from this i'm betting we're gonna
get about
three quarters a cup of fresh
squeezed carrot juice
so there we go all this uh pulp you know
you could
feed to an animal you could put into
your compost if you want you can make
crackers or something out of it
and we'll just pour this into the
vitamix container
let's see how close i was see pretty
spot on right around three quarters of a
cup
so to this we're going to make the curry
sauce so what we're going to do is add
300 grams of tomatoes now i'm using
grape tomatoes because i have an
abundance of them but any tomatoes will
do
the more flavorful the more flavorful
the sauce is going to be
the more flavorful the sauce is going to
be so put those tomatoes in there
i have 35 grams of onion you could use
any onion sweet onion green onion you
could omit the onion if you don't want
that
powerful flavor 35 grams of ginger i
love ginger putting a bunch of ginger in
there i'm not going to bother peeling it
or anything like that this is good
quality organic ginger
boom right in there one clove of garlic
boom i like it spicy guys i like spicy
so i have three of these green chilies
you know go to your tolerance level i'll
have the full written recipe in the
instructions linked below and
i want my curry sweets so i'm putting in
six of these little dates which is
actually about the same as
three medjool dates about 30 grams i'm
putting those in there
and i have this delicious curry powder
it's a pure hot indian curry powder
check it out it's a pretty darn good
quality one i got for a really darn good
deal
and i'm going buck on this because this
is a curry sushi i want to be
really curious so i'm going to do four
tablespoons yeah you heard that right
four tablespoons of curry so one
two three
four bam yeah no joke
and then i have a
quarter cup of hemp seeds and a quarter
cup of flax seeds now
i'm not gonna put all of that in there
i'm actually going to put about a third
just a rough third in there so
put a little bit of the hemp a little
bit of the flax
can always add more later if we want and
we're going to blend that up and see how
smooth that gets
wow it smells and looks divine
let's just see
that's really damn good so the reason i
didn't put all the
flax and the hemp seeds in there is
because i want a little bit of a dipping
sauce on the side
same stuff that's inside just in case i
want more of that flavor so i got a
little bowl here
and i'm going to dump out about a third
of that see it's already fairly thick
the remaining sauce here i want it to be
super thick so it's not just squirting
out of the sushi
so we're actually going to put all the
rest of that back in there all the rest
of the seeds in there and we're going to
blend that up and it'll be more like a
paste
wow so that's really thick
really darn thick like look at that
coating like ah
and it's really dang delicious so as you
can see
tomatoes and mushrooms they dried up
pretty nice so
this way they're gonna suck up the
flavor from the curry instead of
watering it down
it's gonna put all these beautiful
mushrooms
and the tomatoes into this bowl
did you know that mushrooms are the only
plant source of vitamin d
d2 specifically a little vitamin d
supplement i'm gonna
dump this curry sauce right on top look
how thick that is oh
get in there get in there there we go
wow let's give this a stir
i want it to be nicely coated but not to
be like soup
otherwise that's not going to work super
good in sushi rolls so we'll see looks
like i might have made just a little too
much
sauce but it's still gonna work well
again i'm playing this is my first time
ever making this
with these specifications and making it
in this way so
there we go that looks pretty darn good
all right so we have the rice
we have the curry filling we have a
dipping sauce
and we also have an avocado here so what
i'm gonna do
is chop the avocado
in half
i'm gonna try and make five sushi snakes
or five sushi blogs so
i'm gonna cut each half into five slices
so that each
sushi gets two pieces of avocado so
slice one two
three four five so not perfectly
even but we do our best right
avocado is optional you don't have to
add it but
it's pretty darn nice and sushi i
ordered this stuff from
raw nori.com i'm not an affiliate or
anything so you can't help my banana
habit by getting it but
you can get raw vegan nori certified
organic
there you go pretty darn good stuff i
bought a couple bags of these 50 sheets
so that i
can make sushi for the next while i had
them shipped up to sweden and shipped
here so
get them all over so we're gonna go five
so we got five
sushi sheets slip this handy sushi
roller underneath one of them
this is a really useful tool for making
sushi i mean that's what they use
right so i'm gonna slide that underneath
one of these guys
nori's a great source of many different
minerals including
iodine so i don't mind having some of it
every once in a while you want to make
sure you get good quality stuff
i actually have a whole video on better
than nori
because at the time i made that video i
couldn't find certified raw vegan
organic
nori and i was concerned because a lot
of norway can actually have
crushed crustaceans and other little
steam adder inside there and it's
very questionably vegan if it's not
really specifically sourced that way so
this stuff pretty awesome and the better
than nori sheets that i made it has
a whole recipe video so you can actually
look at the link below it's a recipe
video to make your own
non-seaweed nori if you just don't want
seaweed in general
tell you honestly it is better than nori
it is better than nori i make it a lot
of the farm of life it's
really delicious so below you can check
out that recipe too
a little bowl of water on the side
you'll see why soon
and all i'm going to do holy and i don't
know why this video is so long
i don't know i'm talking so much but
yeah all i'm doing is just dividing the
rice between these five sushi rolls
and then flattening it out so that you
can roll them i
swear i will never make a video this
long again i'm
i'm just talking the absolute whole way
through
yep there we go so all i'm doing is just
spreading this out across the sushi
rolls to make some really big curry
sushis that's it
i love it now all we have left is
put these avocado bits in there so
seriously look at that looks amazing
hopefully you can see it it's time to
try and roll these suckers
up so i have this beautiful plate
on standby and what i'm going to do is
start to roll this oh god oh god
it's really going to be a full full one
but there we go that's looking like it's
going to work
no good hopefully it's going to work and
we'll use some water
and seal the end with a bit of water
that way the
sushi paper will actually stick together
so wow that was a messy one
but it's together hopefully the next
ones work a little nicer
so look at that we got these five
beautiful somewhat messy sushi snakes
going on
i'm gonna pause clean up this a little
bit and then we're gonna dive into this
i'll let you know how it is
oh stay tuned for the full nutritional
breakdown here look at that
look at those rolls they're sushi snakes
now i'm lazy i'm not going to cut them
up into individual pieces
you definitely can might be a little
tricky with the insides but
it would work i'm just kind of lazy and
i like to eat them this way kind of like
sushi burritos
so we'll just take one of these guys
right here look at that
oh it's dripping rice a little bit let's
just go for it
dip that down in there and dip it right
in there you know
oh yeah oh my god
wow you know after that talk about
chewing your drink and drinking your
food like gandhi said
you know i'm gonna follow it especially
the video right you know maybe sometimes
i t-rex that snake that
down you know but well
this is damn good i gotta say really
damn tasty
um it's up to play with you know whether
you follow exactly to a tea or you just
utilize this as a bit of a fun
fusion and play with your own
ingredients maybe use different
vegetables inside
of the curry you know really dang
good so i'm gonna enjoy this and go
watch star trek discovery with my
parents tonight so
if you're watching the recipe video
portion then look out for the
nutritional information coming
next for this recipe and the whole day
all right so here's that final meal and
after this we're going to go into even
more detail on the entire day's worth of
food intake so
here you can see i got 1352 calories
just
from this meal you can see the the
breakdown of
all the different ingredients i listed
absolutely every single thing in here
try and get as accurate as possible next
you can see that i got 58 grams of
protein here so
well over half my normal daily intake
106.6 net carbs and
66 grams of fat so a little bit of a
higher fat day but you'll see how that
evens out when it's all together
next here 91 of all my targets just with
this
meal so you can see all of these major
micronutrients
i met you know except for calcium which
we know from the other ones i'm well
over 100
as well so let's go into the whole day's
worth of nutritional calculations
all right now it's time to get into the
nitty gritty of the entire day
and much more detail so you can see here
i got around 4117
calories it's a little more than i'd get
on average but it was a pretty
busy day actually and my needs they can
fluctuate between 2500 to 4000 depending
on my activity level
so you can see i added in all of the
ingredients from all the meals got the
bananas and kale for breakfast or lunch
and the mandarin orange and the kombucha
for the pre-dinner
plus all the ingredients in there for
the
sushi recipe plus i had one spray of
vitamin b12
garden of life i usually take a spray
from that you know
every two to four days just to top off
my vitamin b12
we'll go into the details now so protein
seven percent of my total calories
76 of my total calories from carbs and
my total calories from fat it's a little
higher than average for my fat i usually
fluctuate between 7 to 15 but
this is a little bit of an indulgence
day and in general i float around the 80
10 variable which you know it does have
a little bit of a leeway there
over the week month and even year so
we're looking down here again a little
bit of a surplus in the calories but
that's all good this wasn't uh
completely formulated to how much
exercise i had in there
so looking at the protein 97.9 grams of
protein
non-cooked protein that means no
denatured protein
very bioavailable 715 grams of carbs and
80 grams of fat
that's pretty damn awesome looking at
the highlighted targets
over 400 of my fiber 100 of all my
targets it says
over 380 of my iron over 175 percent of
my calcium
over 1700 of my vitamin a good thing the
body can excrete that
very easily in the urine wow it's 1 619
percent of my vitamin c
396 of my folate 391 of my potassium
doing
really darn good obviously i'm in the
red zone with the energy
and tons of water my needs are filled
and i will actually mention that i had
water to start the day and i had water
after working out and i had some water
just before my smoothie so got a lot of
water in there
you can see all my vitamins here all of
them are in abundance
wow 20 000 of my b12 right that's one
spray there it's amazing that you need
that much in order to absorb just a
very little all the rest looks really
great there with all the vitamins
k really high e vitamin c again
look at all the minerals here all of
them are
at least in the triple digits over 100
percent the sodium
being low which is really good but all
natural
plant sodium 182 percent of my zinc
selenium 256 some of that would be from
the mushrooms
carbohydrates is showing you know i hit
definitely my carbohydrate fix
my fat fix i went a little bit over it
showing but it's actually showing here
that i have a really good three to six
balance it's almost one to one which is
pretty darn amazing
just a little bit of saturated fat going
into all the proteins
setting 141 percent of my protein needs
on an 80 10 10 type approach here every
single
amino acid essential amino acid easily
hit
the lowest one being a hundred and
sixty-two percent of methyl thione so
well i hope you guys really enjoyed the
video and all the breakdown and the
nutritional information and you try out
these recipes and play in the kitchen
have
fun you know if you have any questions
at all just leave a question or a
comment below let me know what you want
to see more of
hit that bell you know if you want to be
notified for the next video and of
course subscribe
right so hope you guys have an awesome
holiday season there's of course going
to be more to come but we're in that
black friday season and
all the links that i mentioned are down
below so you're gonna want to take
advantage of all those so
as always wishing you much peace love
and seasonal fruit
what i eat in a day video
damn that was good don't forget to check
out my raw recipes playlist in the top
left the video just for you in the top
right subscribe for more videos in the
bottom right and get your three free
ebooks in the bottom
left grab your free raw recipe app
available on iphone and android with
over 100 free raw recipes common fruit
and vegetable calorie breakdown freaking
raw some food combining
shopping cart function and so much more